Surviving Sid is a animation, comedy, tv movie film directed by Karen Disher.
Sid the Sloth takes a school of children out on a camping trip from home, only to find that in typical Sid
style, he is not a very good guide and the children he takes with him don't have a very good time.
Sid (voice), played by John Leguizamo.
Scrat (voice), played by Chris Wedge.
Whiny Beaver Boy (voice), played by Shane Baumel.
Smarty Pants Molehog Boy (voice), played by Paul Butcher.
Glyptodon Boy (voice), played by Sean S. Cunningham.
S'more (voice), played by Karen Disher.
Surviving Sid is a 2008 animated short film from Blue Sky Studios, starring
Sid the Sloth of Ice Age and a cameo appearance by Scrat.
It is the third in the series of Ice Age short films, the
other two being Gone Nutty and No Time for Nuts.
Unlike the first two Ice Age short films, Surviving Sid focuses on
Sid and a small animal group of camping children.
Directed by Galen Tan Chu and Karen Disher, the short premiered
on December 9, 2008, on the Horton Hears a Who!
DVD and Blu-ray.
The film explores themes of sloth, ice age, short film.
The tone is lighthearted.